The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
This place is heaven for a devil like me.
That fiend definitely can’t get in.
Once I turn all these fools into my underlings,
I’ll strike back
and kill that fiend !
You ate my stuff
so from now on we’re brothers, right ?
You’ve gotta listen to me, understand ?
No ! Don’t fight over it !
You’re all my underlings now !
Respect me !
Go !
As I thought...
Even if I have a physical body,
I'm also a Soul Devourer when I'm in this Nirvana Space.
I can still devour and command wandering souls.
How can this be ?
My underlings !
My great ambitions !
The fiend is too terrifying...
Master, I knew you wanted to devour them
so I scattered some bait to lure them over.
There are many wandering souls in the trial
but no Soul Devourers.
That means no one can stop me in the third trial.
Find the Soul Formation cultivators that entered here.
I want them alive.
You’re pushing me too far...
Heaven-Slaying Demon Palm !
If it weren't for that brat causing my cultivation to plummet,
how could I have fallen to such a state ?
Now I'm even forced to use the Heaven Sealing Pagoda...
Do the heavens want me dead ?
Found him.
Hand over the inheritance treasure.
Senior,
I don’t know what inheritance treasure you are talking about.
Without the inheritance treasure,
how did you enter
and how will you leave ?
With a set of hand seals.
When Junior last came here,
I found and memorized a set of hand seals.
This set of hand seals
can only be used next to the gate that the end of a trial.
Could you take me to that gate ?
I’ll give you the set of hand seals.
If you kill me, you’ll never get it !
It’s you !
Brat, what the hell did you find in the Land of the Ancient God
that turned you into this ?
Little friend, let’s talk !
We can leave together !
I'll give it to you !
Hunchback Meng ?
He actually didn’t die ?
Master said
that no one is allowed to live through the third trial !
Hunchback Meng actually came back from the dead.
This Land of the Ancient God is too weird.
The wandering souls’ attacks are useless...
Divine Sense,
explode !
Even my Divine Sense attack was useless...
Something's wrong with him.
I have no idea what that thing is
but it's even more terrifying than before.
It looks like he doesn't have a Divine Sense,
he’s no longer human !
Master, what should we do ?
Hunchback Meng killed Duanmu Ji.
It seems he wants to kill all the intruders in the third trial.
I cannot rely on Divine Sense attacks.
With my Core Formation cultivation, I have no chance.
It looks like I'll need to divert him with something else.
Anger !
My cultivation has fallen.
I need to completely rely on you for this third trial.
Return.
Very good,
I didn't waste 1000 years refining you into a puppet.
Cunning brat,
you dare to show yourself before me ?
Kill him ! Kill him now !
You can control the wandering souls !?
Anger !
You damn brat,
what the hell did you do ?
Once I catch you,
I’ll cast you into the hell of desires
never to be reborn !
Thank you, Senior.
There's another one !
That’s wonderful !
Hunchback Meng, why are you looking like a ghost ?
Master said
that I'll be rewarded for killing people in the third trial.
His Divine Sense is gone.
The old hunchback was refined into a high-level puppet.
You're in the way !
This cultivation...
You... you’re already Late stage Soul Formation ?
Desire Blood Escape Technique ?
Useless !
Six Desires, activate !
This Turtle Bone Puppet
is too weak !
How is this possible ?
How is this possible !?
Who the hell are you !?
Who dares to harm my disciple ?
Sky Devil Magician\NXuan Tian Sect Ancestor\NLate stage Soul Formation
Master !
Yi’er, do you still recognize me ?
Very good.
Master, it’s been 1000 years !
You’re still alive !
You’re really still alive !
How dare you defy Master’s orders ?
An insect that couldn't retain his consciousness
dares to lecture me ?
For harming Yi'er,
you deserve to die by a thousand cuts.
But you're already dead, it's all the same.
As Duanmu Ji said,
this set of hand seals can only be used at the gate.
This is bad !
The hand seals failed.
You are...
a Soul Devourer ?
Good.
Tuo Sen\NTu Si's demon\N8-stars Ancient God
My Demon Puppets,
capture this Soul Devourer.
Bring him here.
Weird... Where did that Soul Devourer go ?
Soul Devourer ?
These people are here to capture me.
Could it be...
What are you doing here ?
we are obeying Master's orders
to capture that Soul Devourer.
Did you get him ?
What are you standing there for ?
Who will take responsibility
if it takes too long ?
Master ?
Didn’t the Ancient God die long ago ?
Who is this Master ?
Everyone’s gone, come out.
Master, what’s going on ?
Six Desires Devil Lord’s Master isn’t dead either ?
Actually, there's no treasure to find in the Land of the Ancient God.
It’s been a trap from the very beginning.
What... what does this mean ?
After I died,
I woke up in the Blood Sea
and came back from the dead
with this appearance.
Only then
did I learn the truth of the Land of the Ancient God.
Long ago
A cultivator named Tuo Sen
fought a great battle against Ancient God Tu Si
to obtain his inheritance.
Using his last remaining strength,
Tu Si sealed Tuo Sen in the Blood Sea inside his Sea of Consciousness.
Tuo Sen was not willing to accept this
so he set a trap in the Land of the Ancient God
and spread rumors
to attract countless cultivators.
Anyone who dies in the Land of the Ancient God
will be reborn in the Blood Sea
and become his puppet.
The reason he's doing this
is to slowly expel the seal out of his body
and transfer it to others.
He is waiting for the day the seal loosens
to break free
and regain his freedom.
You didn’t die so you could've used the hand seals to escape.
But now, Tuo Sen has completely sealed the Land of the Ancient God.
To leave, you'll need to gamble.
Don’t be afraid my disciple,
Master is here.
Even if I have to risk my life,
I will definitely get you out of here.
Master...
Stay close to me.
With blood as the guide
and veins as the source.
Break !
This overwhelming desire...
What a sinister technique !
Follow me.
Count the specks of time
floating down gently.
The carving knife in your hands etches out destiny.
Forever lock away the scars
of this mortal life.
This fleeting youth is a thing of the past.
The flying bird could not escape the twilight
that fills the sky with a myriad of colors.
The night-blooming flower cannot drink
the crystalization of the golden wind and the jade dew.
I will ask the heavens who exactly
sliced open this world
to let the rain fall in.
I will refine the world
to make our palm lines say
that we will live forever.
Walking off the beaten path
through heaven and earth.
Before returning to dust,
I will refine this mortal body.
The left shore is the joyous laughter
that can brighten up a thousand years of sadness.
The right shore is an eternal silence
lingering under the candlelight.
To overturn this fate,
I will walk against the heavens.
I will even gather the clouds
to illuminate the sky for you.
All this sadness was not meaningless.
How many lives and deaths\Nhave passed in the blink of an eye ?
I vow to break
this chess game of fate.